{
    "subject": "resource/Domaine_Rouse",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Stretford",
    "human_readable": "The birthplace of Domaine Rouse is Stretford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8980042338371277,
            "question": "Stretford is known as the birthplace of what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566286563873291,
            "question": "Is Stretford the hometown of Domaine Rouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8507577180862427,
            "question": "What is the birthplace of Domaine Rouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8454033136367798,
            "question": "Where was Domaine Rouse born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7997705936431885,
            "question": "Can you tell me the place of birth for Domaine Rouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6717579960823059,
            "question": "Domaine Rouse is from Stretford. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5390521287918091,
            "question": "In which location was Domaine Rouse established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3941500782966614,
            "question": "Domaine Rouse originates from where?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34352514147758484,
            "question": "Where did Domaine Rouse come into existence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3111894726753235,
            "question": "What city is associated with Domaine Rouse's origin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birthplace of Domaine Rouse is Stretford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8241_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Domaine Rouse come into existence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8241_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Domaine Rouse originates from where?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8241_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which location was Domaine Rouse established?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8241_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8241_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information that confirms Domaine Rouse was born in Stretford, England, United Kingdom (as stated in both file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8241/re-ranker-msmarco/96.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8241/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context clearly states that \"Domaine Rouse - Born on July 4, 1989 - Association football player\" and further specifies \"Place of Birth: Stretford\". Therefore, the statement \"The birthplace of Domaine Rouse is Stretford\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}